(audience applauds)
(upbeat music)
♪ Do you believe in magic
in a young girl's heart ♪
♪ How the music can free
her whenever it starts ♪
♪ And it's magic if
the music is groovy ♪
♪ It makes you feel happy
like an old-time movie ♪
♪ I'll tell you about the magic,
and it'll free your soul ♪
♪ But it's like trying
to tell a stranger ♪
♪ 'Bout rock and roll ♪
♪ If you believe in magic,
don't bother to choose ♪
♪ If it's jug band music
or rhythm and blues ♪
♪ Just go and listen,
it'll start with a smile ♪
♪ It won't wipe off your face
no matter how hard you try ♪
♪ Your feet start tapping
and you can't seem to find ♪
♪ How you got there, so
just blow your mind ♪
(guitar solo)
♪ If you believe in magic,
come along with me ♪
♪ We'll dance until morning
'til there's just you and me ♪
♪ And maybe, if the
music is right ♪
♪ I'll meet you tomorrow,
sort of late at night ♪
♪ And we'll go dancing,
baby, then you'll see ♪
♪ How the magic's in the
music and the music's in me ♪
♪ Yeah, do you
believe in magic ♪
♪ Yeah, believe in the magic
of a young girl's soul ♪
♪ Believe in the magic
of rock and roll ♪
that can set you free ♪
♪ Ohh, talking 'bout the magic ♪
♪ Like I believe in magic
(Do you believe in magic) ♪
♪ Do you believe
like I believe ♪
(audience cheers)